甩不掉背上的泼猴吗？
Can't get the monkey off your back?
那就放进嘴里吧
Then put it in your mouth...
美味的金猴啤酒
with Monkeyshine Beer!
哇噢
Wow.
金猴啤酒
Monkeyshine Beer.
外头就是宽广的丛林
Because it's a jungle out there!
每次看到这个广告我就难过
That commercial always makes me so sad.
可是那个男的一打开啤酒 女人就对他投怀送抱
Yeah, but then the guy opens his beer and girls run at him...
结局很棒啊
so everything works out okay.
我的意思是 那只猴子让我想到马塞尔
I meant because the monkey in it reminds me of Marcel.
我了解
I can see that.
因为他们都有棕色眼睛跟翘下巴
Because they both have those big brown eyes and the little pouty chin.
而且他们都是猴子？
And the fact that they're both monkeys?
有时我会想把他送走是对的吗？
I wonder if I did the right thing, giving him away.
罗斯 你只能这样做 他看到什么就跳上去
Ross, you had to. He was humping everything in sight.
害我的马里布芭比娃娃 不能穿着白纱参加婚礼了
I mean, I have a Malibu Barbie who will no longer be wearing white to her wedding.
还记得他会把你们的帽子借走
Remember when he'd borrow your hat...
拿回来之后 上面都是猴大便吗？
and when you got it back, there'd be little monkey raisins in it?
他那样做很好玩 我对我老板那样做的时候…
When he did it, it was funny. When I did it to my boss's hat...
却被老板责怪我态度不佳
All of a sudden, I had this big "attitude problem."
没有人告诉你活着有多累
∮ So no one told you life was gonna be this way ∮
上班受罪 口袋空空 爱情变累赘
∮ Your job's a joke, you're broke, your love life's D.O.A. ∮
寂寞又潦倒 受气又受累
∮ It's like you're always stuck in second gear ∮
日复一日 年复一年
∮ When it hasn't been your day, ∮
时运不济 活着受罪
∮ your week, your month, or even your year ∮
你我永不离弃
∮ but I'll be there for you ∮
纵有狂风暴雨
∮ When the rain starts to pour ∮
你我永不离弃
∮ I'll be there for you ∮
支持一如往昔
∮ Like I've been there before ∮
你我永不离弃
∮ I'll be there for you ∮
你我相偎相依
∮ 'Cause you're there for me too ∮
嘿…
Hey. Hey.
- 你们猜猜看我拿着什么？ - 韵律？
- Check it out! Guess what I got?     - Rhythm?
不是 是第一封影迷来信啦
No. My first fan mail!
来看看
Check it out.
"亲爱的雷莫瑞医生
"Dear Dr. Ramoray:
要知道我爱你 我愿不惜一切得到你"
Know that I love you and would do anything to have you."
天啊 "你的公开崇拜者 艾瑞卡福特"
My gosh! "Your not-so-secret admirer, Erika Ford."
等等
Oh, wait.
"附注 请收下我送的14根睫毛"
"P.S. Enclosed, please find 14 of my eyelashes."
在疯狂世界 这样代表你已经结婚了
You know, in Crazy World, that means you're married.
这封信不是寄到《我们的日子》剧组 收信地址是你家耶
It's not addressed to Days Of Our Lives. This came to your apartment.
上面没有邮戳 她就藏身在我们大楼里
There's no stamp on it. This woman was in our building.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
我竟然有自己的跟踪者了
I got my very own stalker!
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey, guys.     - Hey.
- 嘿   - 噢
- Hey.     - Ooh.
你要去哪里？
Where are you off to?
我要去参加洛杉矶的 古生物学研讨会
There's this paleontology conference in L.A.
我想顺便去动物园给马塞尔惊喜
So I figured I'd go and drive down to the zoo and surprise Marcel.
我想他会很惊喜的 直到发现他自己是只猴子
I think he will be surprised. Till he realizes he's a monkey...
不会有那种情感
and, uh, you know, isn't capable of that emotion.
菲比？那个帅哥又来了
Oh, Phoebe? That really cute guy is here again.
哦？噢
Oh? Oh.
喔 各位…
Okay, so everyone, ahem...
请假装我在跟你们说故事 而且是很好笑的故事
pretend I'm telling you a story and it's really funny.
大家快笑啊 快
So everyone just laugh. Now!
我知道 对啊
I know, I know! Oh.
- 哈罗   - 嗨
- Hello.     - Hi.
噢
Oh.
我是罗伯·杜南
I'm Rob Donan.
嗨 罗伯·杜南
Hi, Rob Donan.
我对音乐一窍不通 不过我觉得你非常棒
I don't know anything about music, but I think you're really great.
喔 哇
Oh, wow. Ha, ha.
我负责帮儿童图书馆安排表演
Anyway, I schedule performers for children's libraries.
我想问你有没有考虑过 为孩子们演唱
And I was thinking, have you thought about playing your songs for kids?
我是很想有小孩…
Oh, I would love to have kids...
在小孩面前表演我写给他们的歌
hear me play the songs that I will write for them.
晚餐吃什么？
What do you wanna do for dinner?
我们可以留在家自己煮
We could stay in and cook for ourselves.
- 哈罗   - 我是艾瑞卡
- Hello.     - It's Erika.
天啊 是那个跟踪者
Oh, my God. The stalker!
不用了 门没关
Never mind. It's open.
啊 啊
Aah! Aah!
拿锅子打她 好主意啊
Yes, hitting her with a frying pan is a good idea.
可是还得再有一个备用计划 以免她不像卡通人物一样容易被打倒
We might wanna have a backup plan, though, just in case she isn't a cartoon.
我们快逃离这里吧
Let's get out of here!
竟然挑这个时候不在家
The one time they're not home!
好 好
Okay. Okay.
我们要走 在楼梯上碰到的时候…
We'll leave. When we pass her...
…她不会知道是我 因为我们没有见过啊
she won't know me, because we never met!
只有广播明星能这样摆脱跟踪者
That's how radio stars escape stalkers!
她来了
She's coming!
- 是我   - 噢
- It's me.     - Aah!
完了 我们要因此送命了
Uh, this is it. This is how we're gonna die.
- 准备好没？ - 等一下
- You ready?     - Wait, wait, wait!
嗨
Hi.
艾瑞卡
Erika!
- 盖勒先生？ - 是 嗨
- Mr. Geller?     - Yes, hi.
嗨 我是狄恩·利浦森 动物园园长
Hi. Dean Lipson, zoo administrator.
我听说你有个问题
I was told you had a question.
我找不到去年捐给动物园的猴子
I, uh... I can't find the monkey I donated last year. He's a capuchin...
一只叫马塞尔的卷尾猴？
answers to the name Marcel?
恐怕我得告诉你坏消息
Ah. I'm afraid I have some bad news.
马塞尔已经过世了
Marcel has passed on.
天啊 怎么了？
Oh, my God. What happened?
他生了病 病情越来越恶化…
Well, he got sick, and then he got sicker...
后来状况有一点好转
and then he got a little better.
可是最后他还是死了
But then he died.
我真是不敢相信
I can't believe this!
我很遗憾 盖勒先生 俗话说的好
I'm sorry, Mr. Geller. But you know, there's an old saying:
"猴子难免一死"
"Sometimes monkeys die."
虽然这不是句了不起的话
It's not a great saying...
可是很适合用在今天这种状况
but it certainly is fitting today.
- 你们应该打电话通知我的   - 抱歉
- Someone should've called me.     - I'm sorry.
我知道这样无法挽回他的生命
Look, I know this can't bring him back...
不过这是我们的一点心意
but here, it's just a gesture.
动物园代币？
Zoo dollars?
是啊 你可以参观4点的小鸟秀 金刚鹦鹉戴帽子表演
Yes, and come see the bird show at 4. The macaws wear hats.
如果你的猴子没死就更好了
Well, it's a lot cuter if your monkey hasn't just died.
噢
Ooh.
我知道
I know.
乔伊竟然和跟踪者吃午餐
I can't believe Joey's having lunch with his stalker.
她长得怎么样？
What is she like?
- 记得《战栗游戏》里的凯西·贝兹吗？ - 嗯
- Well, you remember Kathy Bates in Misery?     - Mm-hm.
她跟她长的完全相反
Well, she looks the exact opposite of that.
她没疯吗？
And she's not crazy?
不是 她是个超级大疯子
Oh, no, no. She's a total wack job.
她认为乔伊就是德瑞克·雷莫瑞医生
Yeah. She thinks that Joey is actually Dr. Drake Ramoray.
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
这样他还跟她约会？
Oh. And he's going out with her?
他这样是不行的
He cannot pursue this.
仅仅因为这个女人以为她可以在她的客厅通过魔盒看到乔伊…
Just because this woman thinks she can see Joey through the magical box...
并不表示她就不是人
in her living room doesn't mean she's not a person.
她难道没有权利去爱 不能追求幸福吗？
Does she not deserve happiness? Does she not deserve love?
你们干嘛瞪我啊？是他自己要去跟疯子约会的
What are you looking at me for? He's the one who wants to boff the maniac.
你还好吧？
Are you okay?
不好 我很紧张
No, uh-uh. I'm just nervous.
如果我想像他们只穿着内衣裤
Maybe if I just picture them all in their underwear...
这样不太好 上个表演者就是这样被开除的
That's not a good idea. That's the reason the last guy got fired.
噢
Oh.
好
Yeah.
我只是习惯在大人面前表演
I'm used to playing for grownups.
大人会边喝咖啡 边忙着自己的事情
Grownups drink their coffee and do their grownup thing, you know.
可是小孩子
And kids...
会认真听表演
listen.
这样我的责任太大了
It's just a huge responsibility.
怎么样？
What?
你要亲我吗？
Are you gonna kiss me?
我是有这个打算
I was thinking about it.
好
Okay.
好了 开始表演罗
Yeah, okay. Alrighty. Let's play some tunes!
嗨 大家好 我是菲比
Hi, everybody. I'm Phoebe.
嗨 菲比
Hi, Phoebe!
好吧
Ha, ha. Okay. Um...
我要唱一首关于爷爷奶奶的歌 好吗？
I'm gonna play, um, some songs about grandparents, okay?
奶奶是大家都喜欢的人
Now Grandma's a person Who everyone likes
她会买给你一辆火车跟一辆闪亮脚踏车
She bought you a train And a bright shiny bike
可是最近她一直没来吃晚饭
But lately she hasn't Been coming to dinner
你上次看到她时 她瘦了好多
And last time you saw her She looked so much thinner
爸爸跟妈妈说 她搬去秘鲁
Now your mom and your dad said She moved to Peru
其实她已经死了 有天你也会死
But the truth is she died And someday you will too
啦啦啦啦啦啦 啦啦啦啦啦啦 啦啦啦啦啦啦
La-la-la-la, la-la-la-la La-la-la-la, la-la-la-la-la-la
- 德瑞克 这一切真的很棒 对吧？ - 对啊
- Oh, Drake, isn't it amazing?     - Yeah, it is.
怎么了？
What?
我们现在坐在这里吃饭
Well, here we sit, devil-may-care...
很难想像你刚才还在帮席蒙接脊椎呢
and just a little while ago you were reattaching Simone's spinal cord.
对 那个手术很困难
Yeah, that was a tricky one.
事实上
In reality...
这样的手术要花10小时 不过他们只播出2分钟
that operation takes over 10 hours, but they only showed it for two minutes.
他们是谁？
Who's "they"?
没什么啦
No one.
德瑞克 你好有才华喔 让我看看你的手
Oh, Drake, you are so talented. Let me see those hands.
- 这双手真是美丽   - 哈哈
- Oh, these hands, these beautiful hands.     - Ha, ha.
我好想把这双手给吃了
Ha, ha. Oh, I could just eat them.
- 可是我不会   - 哈哈
- But I won't.     - Ha, ha.
很好 不然我的手表会掉下来
Good. Otherwise my watch would fall off.
我是说真的
No, seriously.
这双手
These hands...
这双神奇 拯救生命的手
these miracle, magical, life-giving hands.
我只想接近它们 碰触它们 甚至舔一下
Oh, just to be near them, touch them, maybe even lick one?
- 好吧 只舔一只喔   - 哈哈
- All right. Ha, ha. Just one.     - Ha-ha-ha.
哇噢
Wow.
你还真厉害
You're good at that.
天啊 来个人 他噎到了
Oh, my God! Someone! He's choking!
这里有人是医生吗？
Is anyone here a doctor?
有
Oh, yes.
这里有塞伦镇最优秀的医生
Yes, the best doctor in Salem!
德瑞克·雷莫瑞医生
Dr. Drake Ramoray!
15分钟后到夜间馆跟我会合
Meet me in the nocturnal house in 15 minutes.
听着 我不喜欢跟男人做那种接触
Uh, hey, look. I don't really enjoy being with other men that way.
你想要动物园代币吗？
But, um, zoo dollars?
是关于你猴子的事情
It's about your monkey.
他还活着
It's alive.
我不懂 你为什么不帮那个人？
I don't understand. Why didn't you help that man?
因为我是神经外科医生…
Uh, because, uh, I'm a neurosurgeon...
而他的状况显然是…
and that was clearly a case of, uh, uh...
"食物噎到症"
"foodal chokage."
你知道…
You know.
- 我有事得跟你说…   - 不 不行
- I gotta tell you something...     - No, no, no.
不 你什么都不用跟我说
You don't have to tell me anything.
你不需要对我解释
You don't have to explain yourself to me. Oh!
我凭什么可以质疑伟大的雷莫瑞医生？
Who am I to question the great Dr. Drake Ramoray?
- 可是…   - 我能接近你就很开心了
- That's...     - I should be happy to be near you.
嘿 我…
Hey, I...
怎么样？
"Hey" what?
没事 只是随口说声嘿
That's it. Just hey!
就像跳完舞之后也会说声"嘿"
Like at the end of a dance. Hey!
嘿
Hey. Ha-ha-ha.
嗨
Hey.
有一天你们会长大
There'll be times when you get older
你们会想跟别人上床
When you'll want to sleep with people
只为博得他们欢心 但不要这么做
Just to make them like you But don't
因为这是…
'Cause
那是另一件你们不该做的事
That's another thing that you don't wanna do
大家一起来
Everybody!
那是另一件你们不该做的事
That's another thing that you don't wanna do
- 太棒了   - 非常有知识性的一首歌
- Excellent!     - Very informative!
一点都不会不恰当
Not at all inappropriate!
谢谢大家来参加 后面有饼干可以吃喔
Thank you for coming, everybody. There are cookies in the back.
你表演的真棒
That was great.
小孩子都很喜欢你
The kids loved you.
我超酷的吧
Yay! I rock!
你知道为什么吗？因为你跟他们说实话
And you know why? Because you told the truth.
从没有人会跟小孩说实话
Nobody ever tells kids the truth.
你真的太了不起了
You were incredible!
可是…？
Ha, ha. But?
- 你怎么知道还有"可是"？ - 我有感应
- How did you know there was a "but"?     - I sense these things.
不是"可是"就是"好话"
It was either "but" or "butter."
问题是 我想有些父母…
The thing is, I think some of the parents...
他们希望
they were hoping that...
你多唱一些跟农场动物有关的歌
you'd play more songs about barnyard animals.
没问题啊
I can do that.
- 真的吗？ - 当然罗
- Really?     - Yeah.
- 因为那样子会非常棒   - 噢
- Because that would be fantastic.     - Oh.
怎样？你想亲我吗？
What? You wanna kiss me?
我的确有这个打算
I'm thinking about it.
喔 蝙蝠
Ah, the bat.
黑暗使者
Ambassador of darkness.
像长了翅膀的使者一般飞出洞中
Flitting out of his cave like a winged messenger.
看不见的幽灵
Sightless specter of the macabre.
老兄 我的猴子？
Buddy, my monkey?
喔 对喔
Oh, yeah, right.
有一桩抢案发生在…
There was a break-in...
几个月前 是监守自盗
a few months back. Inside job.
你的猴子被带走了
Your monkey was taken.
天啊 可是动物园跟我说我的猴子死了
Oh, my God. The zoo told me that my monkey was dead.
动物园
Pfft. The zoo!
你相信动物园的说法吗？
You believe everything the zoo tells you?
可是动物园只跟我说这些啊
Uh, that's the only thing the zoo's ever told me.
他们当然会这样说 因为不希望坏消息传开来
Of course they'll say he's dead. They don't want the bad publicity.
这是个大阴谋
It's all a great big cover-up.
你知道这件事牵扯到很多高层吗？
Do you have any idea how high up this thing goes?
那个叫利浦森的人？
That guy Lipson?
利浦森知道这件事？
Lipson knows?
唔
Hmm.
利浦森知道啊
Lipson knows, huh?
哈罗 负鼠先生
Ah, hello, Mr. Possum.
树上的谜团 爬上爬下的夜行者
Enigma of the trees, upside-down denizen of the night.
- 无视于地心引力…   - 老兄 我的猴子 我的猴子？
- Taunting gravity...     - Buddy, my monkey. My monkey?
街头巷尾传说…
Word on the street...
我所谓的街头巷尾 指的是动物园里的游园道路
Well, when I say "street," I mean those little pretend streets here at the zoo.
我知道
Of course.
听说你的猴子找到新工作
Your monkey found a new career...
而且是在娱乐业 我只知道这么多
in the entertainment field. That's all I know.
这真是令人难以置信
This is unbelievable!
这样的情报值多少钱呢 朋友？
So, what is this information worth to you, my friend?
你是要我贿赂你吗？
Are you trying to get me to bribe you?
可能喔
Maybe.
可是你已经告诉我一切了
But you already told me everything.
你们看 他就是金猴啤酒的那只猴子
Check it out. He actually is the Monkeyshine monkey.
那你打算怎么办？
Oh, wow. So, what are you gonna do?
我要打电话给啤酒公司询问他的下落
I'm gonna call the beer company and try to find out where he is.
我的马不见的时候 我也是这么做的
That's what I did when I lost my Clydesdales.
嗨
Okay, hi again!
嗨 菲比
Hi, Phoebe!
今天要唱一些跟农场动物有关的歌
Today, we're gonna start with some songs about barnyard animals.
草原上的牛"哞哞哞"
Oh, the cow in the meadow goes "moo"
农夫在敲他的头 把他绞成肉酱
Then the farmer hits him on the head And grinds him up
这就是汉堡肉的由来
And that's how we get hamburgers
接下来是鸡
Now chickens
只有你能救她 德瑞克
You're the only one who can save her, Drake!
拜托 我只是个医生 不是神仙
Damn it! I'm a doctor, I'm not God!
我对医生的信赖全没了
Well, there goes my whole belief system.
我是艾瑞卡
It's Erika.
天啊 快把电视关了
Quick! Quick. Shut off the TV.
等下 我想知道剧情发展啊
Wait, I wanna see what happens!
我帮莱丝莉脱离昏迷状态 然后我们就亲热
Uh, I get Leslie out of the coma then we make out.
怎么可能？你刚刚才亲了赛宾娜啊
How can that be? You were just kissing Sabrina.
瑞秋 在那个世界里 乔伊是个神经外科医生
Rachel, it's a world where Joey is a neurosurgeon.
嘿 艾瑞卡 进来吧
Hey, Erika. Come in.
你怎么这么快就到家？我刚还看到你在塞伦
How did you get here so fast? I just saw you in Salem.
喔 他们用直升机送我回来
Right, they, uh, choppered me in. Ha, ha.
怎么啦？
What's up?
你们在开派对啊
Oh, you're having a little party too.
- 她在这里吗？ - 谁啊？
- Is she here, huh, huh?     - Who?
赛宾娜啊 我知道你们的事了
Sabrina. I know about you two!
我看到你在医生休息室亲吻她
I saw you today, kissing in the doctor's lounge.
事情不是你想的那样
It's not what you think. That was...
你还说我是你唯一的爱
You told me I was the only one!
好吧 够了
All right, look. That's it.
我们不该再继续交往了
We shouldn't see each other anymore.
我应该早点告诉你的
I should have told you a long time ago...
我不是德瑞克·雷莫瑞
but I am not Drake Ramoray, okay?
我不是医生 只是演员 我假装自己是个医生
I'm not even a doctor. I'm an actor. I just pretend to be a doctor.
我的天啊 医院的人知道这件事吗？
Oh, my God. Do the people at the hospital know about this?
有人可以帮我一下吗？
Ha, ha. Somebody wanna help me out here?
喔 我知道了
Oh, I know! I know!
我在哪里？
Where am I?
这里是大学附属医院
University Hospital...
你已经在这昏迷18年了
the same place you've been for the last 18 years.
你怎么会同时出现在两个地方？
How can you be here and there?
因为那是电视影集
Ha, ha. Because it's a television show.
德瑞克 你这话是什么意思？
Drake, what are you getting at?
我不是德瑞克
I'm not Drake!
没错 他不是德瑞克 他是…
That's right. He's not Drake. He's...
汉斯·雷莫瑞 德瑞克的邪恶双胞胎兄弟
Hans Ramoray, Drake's evil twin!
这是真的吗？
Is this true?
是 是真的
Yes! Yes, it is true.
我之所以知道是因为…
And I know this...
他假装自己是德瑞克 跟我上床
because he pretended to be Drake to sleep with me!
他还跟我说 他会跟我私奔
And then he told me he would run away with me.
可是他根本没有
And he didn't!
你还没把马桶盖放下来 你这个混蛋
And you left the toilet seat up, you bastard!
这些都是真的吗？
Is all this true?
是的 恐怕是真的
Yes, I'm afraid it is.
我根本配不上你 艾瑞卡
You deserve much better than me, Erika.
你应该跟真正的德瑞克在一起 你爱的是他
You deserve to be with the real Drake. He's the one you fell in love with.
去塞伦找他吧
Go to Salem. Find him!
他才是适合你的人
He's the guy for you.
喔 汉斯
Oh, Hans.
汉斯？
Hans?
汉斯
Hans!
嘿 邪恶双胞胎
Yo, evil twin!
是 再见了 艾瑞卡
Right. Uh, goodbye, Erika.
祝你在塞伦一切顺利
Good luck in Salem.
保重了
Take care.
我永远不会忘记你的 汉斯
I'll never forget you, Hans.
好了 刚泼我水的人
Ha, ha. All right. The people who threw the water!
我们是在帮你耶
Helping you out!
被开除？为什么？
Fired? Why?
图书馆董事会接到很多家长的抱怨
The library board has had a lot of complaints from parents...
- 关于你的歌曲里的一些内容   - 我不敢相信
- about some of the stuff in your songs.     - I can't believe it!
你有跟董事会说孩子们想听实话吗？
Did you tell your board about how the kids want to hear the truth?
没有
No.
我了解了
I see.
如果你唱一些正常的儿歌…
Maybe if you just played some regular kiddie songs?
不要
No.
你希望我变成什么样子？像那些…
What do you want me to be? Like some...
又大又蠢的紫色恐龙吗？
stupid, big, like, purple dinosaur?
你不需要变成邦尼
You don't have to be Barney.
- 邦尼是谁？ - 呃
- Who's Barney?     - Eh...
我追踪到马塞尔 听好了 他很健康也很快乐
Well, I tracked down Marcel and get this: He's healthy, he's happy...
而且他现在在纽约拍 《危机总动员2:病毒席卷曼哈顿》
and he's here in New York filming Outbreak 2: The Virus Takes Manhattan.
- 不会吧   - 不会吧 我的天啊
You're kidding!
- 真是太棒了   - 对啊
- This is amazing.     - I know.
我好不容易才上了电视 那只猴子竟然拍了电影
I finally get a part on TV, and the monkey's making movies.
瑞秋 我准备好了
Okay. Rachel, I'm ready.
好
Okay.
不好意思 请问这里有个会说实话的女歌手吗？
Excuse me. Is this where the singing lady is who tells the truth?
应该就是我
Um, yeah, I guess that's me.
她在这里
She's here!
有时男人爱女人
Sometimes men love women
有时男人爱男人
And sometimes men love men
还有人是双性恋
And then there are bisexuals
虽然有些人会说 他们只是在欺骗自己
Though some just say They're kidding themselves
啦啦啦啦啦 啦啦啦啦啦啦啦
La-la-la-la. La-la-la-la-la-la-la.
啦啦啦啦 啦啦啦啦啦 啦啦
La-la-la-la. La-la-la-la-la, la-la
太令人兴奋了 我已经一年没看到我的猴子了
This is exciting. I haven't seen my monkey in a year.
怎么 你洗澡的时候都没往下看喔？
What, you never look down in the shower?
我不能开 "猴子就是小弟弟"这种玩笑吗？
Oh, please. I'm not allowed to make one joke in the "monkey is penis" genre?
请退后
Back up, please.
退后 快点
Back up. Come on, come on.
不好意思 哪里可以找到那只猴子？
Excuse me. Uh, where can we find the monkey?
不好意思 今天的拍摄不对外开放
I'm sorry. It's a closed set.
你不了解 我是他的朋友
I'm sorry, you don't understand. I'm a friend of his.
我们以前曾经住在一起
We, uh, used to live together.
对 我在波科诺斯也跟飞宝一起住过
Yeah. And I have a timeshare in the Poconos with Flipper.
罗斯 他在那里
Ross, there he is!
嘿 伙伴
Hey! Hey, buddy!
马塞尔 马塞尔
Marcel! Marcel!
在丛林里 广大的丛林 今晚狮子要睡觉
In the jungle, the mighty jungle The lion sleeps tonight
他们不带你去看兽医
They won't take you to the vet
很显然你不是他们最爱的宠物
You're obviously not Their favorite pet
- 臭猫 臭猫   - 臭猫 臭猫
- Smelly cat, smelly cat     - Smelly cat, smelly cat
- 这不是你的错   - 这不是你的错
- It's not your fault     - It's not your fault
不
No
- 怎么了？ - 抱歉
- What?     - I'm sorry.
有什么问题？
What's wrong with that?
我觉得你可能要 唱得有男性气慨一点
Um, ahem, I think you might wanna, like, pick a more masculine note. Heh.